(Sheldon:)Where are my pants?
You might wanna check YouTube.
(Sheldon:)-What do I search?
-It's already loaded. Just hit play.
(On-screen Sheldon:)All right, people,
let's get down to the math.
It is only three-dimensional thinking
that limits our imagination.
(On-screen Sheldon:)Can I take my pants off
over my head?
(On-screen Sheldon:)Of course not,
my body's in the way.
(On-screen Sheldon:)But if we had access
to higher dimensions...
(On-screen Sheldon:)...we could move our pants
around our bodies...
(On-screen Sheldon:)...through the fourth dimension...
(On-screen Sheldon:)...and our days of dropping trousers
would be over.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Lord, this couldn't be
any more humiliating.
Oh. Give it a minute.
(On-screen Sheldon:)Now for the astronomers
in the audience...
(On-screen Sheldon:)...get ready to see the dark side
of the moon.
(On-screen Sheldon:)And here's Uranus.